{
    "id": "c2cc6669319a4e7f9b774f7471d755a0",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We had a press pass but ………………………… refused admittance anyhow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "As he ………………………. older, his mind regressed further into the past.",
            "description": "Use the simple past to talk about two past events that took place simultaneously. ",
            "answers": [
                "gets",
                "got",
                "gotten"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… any regrets over anything I have ever done.",
            "description": "Either don't have or have never had is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "have never",
                "don't have",
                "have never had"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She was made …………………………. the whole story.",
            "description": "Made is followed by a to-infinitive in passive structures.",
            "answers": [
                "repeat",
                "to repeating",
                "to repeat"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Reading books ……………………….. a good hobby.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the ing form reading ing forms are treated as singular. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Suma as well as her sisters ……………………….. at the party.",
            "description": "When we connect two nouns with as well as, the verb agrees with the former.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "John along with his friends ……………………….. in that house.",
            "description": "When we connect two nouns with 'along with', the verb agrees with the former.",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know where ………………………?",
            "description": "In indirect questions, the verb goes after the subject. ",
            "answers": [
                "does he live",
                "he lives",
                "does he lives"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Scarcely …………………………. one project before she started another.",
            "description": "Either had she finished or did she finish is correct here.",
            "answers": [
                "had she finished",
                "did she finish",
                "she finished"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "‘You look tired.’ ‘Yes, I …………………………’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am running",
                "had been running",
                "am running"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Each guest ………………………. welcomed with open arms.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Every student …………………….. handed in their work.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after every.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}